{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452362201","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452362201"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452368844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452368844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452375492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452375491"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452382130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452382129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452388769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452388769"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452395395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452395395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452402050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452402050"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452408696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452408695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_2_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452415352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452415352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452422825","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452422825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452431561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452431561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" d64ae9f7-c009-4f73-8088-1065080d68bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452452209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452452209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" 31ea90f0-54d2-4c85-920f-50fa6d1731a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452455603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452455603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" 31ea90f0-54d2-4c85-920f-50fa6d1731a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452456086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452456085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" 31ea90f0-54d2-4c85-920f-50fa6d1731a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452456271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452456271"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142539"," gameId":" 31ea90f0-54d2-4c85-920f-50fa6d1731a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}